<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FloraFolio</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Lavender">Lavender</string>
    <string name="Account">Account</string>
    <string name="Rose">Rose</string>
    <string name="florafolio">FloraFolio</string>
    <string name="e_mail_address">E-Mail Address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up!</string>
    <string name="my_plants">My Plants</string>
    <string name="upload_new_plant">Upload New Plant</string>
    <string name="hello_name">Hello, Name!</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to FloraFolio!</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="intro">We cover plant diversity for all your gardening knowledge. Let\'s dig into some dirt.</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="lavInfo">"Lavender is a popular and aromatic herb known for its fragrant flowers and various uses. Lavender is well-suited for cultivation in areas with well-drained soil and plenty of sunlight. It is a hardy plant and is often grown in gardens, borders, or as ornamental plants in landscaping.
                Aromatherapy: Lavender essential oil is known for its calming and soothing properties. It is often used in aromatherapy to promote relaxation and alleviate stress. Culinary: Some lavender varieties are used in culinary applications, adding a subtle floral flavor to dishes and desserts. However, not all lavender is suitable for consumption, so it's important to use varieties specifically labeled as culinary lavender.
        Medicinal: Lavender has been used in traditional medicine for its potential anti-inflammatory and antimicrobial properties. Symbolism: Lavender is often associated with calmness, purity, and devotion. It has been used in various cultures for its symbolic and medicinal significance. Some well-known lavender varieties include Lavandula angustifolia (English lavender), Lavandula x intermedia (Lavandin), and Lavandula stoechas (Spanish lavender). Lavender is not only appreciated for its beauty but also for its versatility in various applications, making it a beloved plant in gardens and households worldwide."</string>
    <string name="roseInfo">Roses are woody perennial flowering plants belonging to the genus Rosa, which is part of the Rosaceae family. These beautiful and fragrant flowers have been cultivated for centuries and are one of the most popular and well-known ornamental plants worldwide. There are over a hundred species of roses, and thousands of cultivars and hybrids. Common classifications include hybrid teas, floribundas, grandifloras, climbers, shrubs, and miniature roses. Roses are known for their symmetrical, five-petaled flowers, typically with a central cluster of stamens. Colors range from red, pink, and white to yellow, orange, and various shades in between. Roses have been cultivated for their beauty and symbolism for centuries, representing love, passion, and various emotions. They have a significant role in art, literature, and cultural traditions worldwide. Roses thrive in well-drained soil with adequate sunlight. Proper pruning, watering, and pest control are essential for healthy rose bushes.</string>
</resources>