<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FloraFolio</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Lavender">Lavender</string>
    <string name="Account">Account</string>
    <string name="Rose">Rose</string>
    <string name="florafolio">FloraFolio</string>
    <string name="e_mail_address">E-Mail Address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up!</string>
    <string name="my_plants">My Plants</string>
    <string name="upload_new_plant">Upload New Plant</string>
    <string name="hello_name">Hello, Name!</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to FloraFolio!</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="intro">We cover plant diversity for all your gardening knowledge. Let\'s dig into some dirt.</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="lavInfo">"Lavender is well-suited for cultivation in areas with well-drained soil and plenty of sunlight. It is a hardy plant and is often grown in gardens, borders, or as ornamental plants in landscaping.
                \n Aromatherapy: It is often used in aromatherapy to promote relaxation and alleviate stress.
        \n Culinary: Some lavender varieties are used in culinary applications, adding a subtle floral flavor to dishes and desserts. However, not all lavender is suitable for consumption, so it's important to use varieties specifically labeled as culinary lavender.
        \n Medicinal: Lavender has been used in traditional medicine for its potential anti-inflammatory and antimicrobial properties."</string>
    <string name="roseInfo">"Roses are known for their symbol of love, beauty, elegance, fragrance and variety of colors ranging from red, pink, and white to yellow, orange. Roses thrive in well-drained soil with adequate sunlight. Proper pruning, watering, and pest control are essential for healthy rose bushes.
        \n Aromatherapy: Often used to reduce stress, anxiety, and promote relaxation. The sweet and floral scent of rose oil is known for its mood-enhancing effects.
        \n Culinary:Rose water is a byproduct of the distillation of rose essential oil. It is commonly used in culinary applications, especially in Middle Eastern and Asian cuisines. It adds a subtle floral flavor to desserts, beverages, and certain savory dishes.
        \n Medicinal: The fruit of the rose, known as rose hips, is rich in vitamin C and may be used in herbal teas, jams, and supplements for potential immune-boosting properties."</string>
</resources>